Hi
oh yes today Okay
Kemen It's already very late Okay wait
12.00 your status want to make baked
potatoes
eh travel money no
I want to look for the best insurance
in Indonesia clip The research of
Lies the best insurance in Indonesia
we still on Google on what insurance
in the parent that is good
we check on Google
tomorrow insurance
Well there are so many this is reluctant
eyebrow there are many Hi
but maybe we should look for first
there is
we what is called
should it follow or join how much
insurance CV sells if we live it
must join insurance by what insurance are
we required to follow we let's check first
Beijing we check
now
transparency that must be
owned
by Ternate Okay we click Hi
characteristics of transparency for families
there is life insurance the first
health insurance education insurance and also
vehicle insurance home property that well
Why do we have to
the question is Why do
we have to
Amen what is it called
to
participate in that insurance In
my personal opinion yes these are
subjective ideas can be right can be
wrong but in my personal opinion I am like this
still surrender to insurance because
this world
no one can predict What
will happen in the future with
like
So we are
Junior  Insurance is like saving,
saving, just asking, if saving,
if contact lenses, for example, I'm just
starting out, there are a lot of frames like 9,
what's the difficulty, can the car be there?
Forgotten,
what's the name,
good, get a replacement, if you can claim
it, yes, and before joining insurance,
we have to renew it the year before tomorrow,
besides being used in insurance, we
first
check the terms that must be
known, namely,
first,
premium, that's the obligation paid
by the insured party, the insurance customer
to this insurance company, so the
premium is how many rupiah
we have to pay, we are the insurance party, so the
insurance policy blender
is the MB galya document, the relationship between the
insurance company's siblings,
so it's like an insurance policy, it's like a
cooperation agreement, the calculation of entertainment
So what can we claim,
the rules, morning insurance policy, claim,
that claim, yes, usually the clip, if yes, we
are Maung Iklim, claiming our insurance,
so it's not something we must know
before we want to join insurance
Now let's try to check
health insurance, yes, the
best health insurance
in Indonesia, well, there are
lots of them, yes, these are the 10
best health insurances,
yes, there is signal healthy protection,
there is AXA Mandiri Smart car executive, there is
Lippo hofos family Simas healthy  My
BRI Life simple shop hospitality
backpropagation
you guys Smart half this is like and paid
Muenchen yes
then there is also He continues Benny love
Optima cashpoint God
we try to find out one by one yes so
try this first let's
check here first
Hi
signa
still
stubborn Indonesia
here is
this
Indonesia
9 no you guys well
this
Hi this yes
how much I can't Bang
Songo Rusdi this
Syahrini
can't what do you
have to fill again honestly don't need
by the
gedebok tree the explanation is also yes
replacement Let the
builder's imagination be heavy per day replacement of
purchase costs starting from also Millions of people
this dude if for what is it called like
for a cesarean operation to be this one use
this
emergency evacuation for example Usually
if I'm
hospitalized, usually I
with
1.5 million it seems I've been admitted to
Doctor Sutomo to the hospital
good hospital here
hidden there is this AXA Mandiri
Smartfren executive
Okay from the many choices
we can choose
fish if I look at it cheerful
alliance what is this reading Solo fishermen
I understand
Rawa pingin become  can cover even
up to hospitalization up to 500-1000
million and a half after the water is ready
just imagine by vemmy Sagita being
hospitalized with that only paying 400
thousand per month but all
our citizens are itching to use it my plan after
this you know want to go to Hai this is
my Dad BPJS in my opinion how is it
not good enough to pick me up reduce
this insurance for health it's good for
us well here
he is also this BNI Life Optima Kasman
also goyang n also yours Iran
also yes there are so
many Liye competing among themselves
alone
these
insurances are indeed
so Indonesia is indeed a lack of
awareness of the people to
participate in insurance
Jalan siip dirincikan Do you feel that
the cellphone if for example feels like the
money Singing by paying but
not immediately feel the benefits
directly like that Even though in Indonesia
the level of health is still low yes
so If you have money yes
CCTV for expansion I don't remember
anymore health is more important
that if from Choices
1-8 that I see here it's okay all of them
but it seems more
This is Akshay Okay
Then the
signal is also okay, the signal earlier was
Shimasuka okay,
Cinema XXI is still
this B Simas, where is
he Cheap, cute, where is 100,000, he
National Team as The
[Music]
Sims Sinarmas money
Thank you Mas, that's Sinarmas, I just
found out,
you guys are students Alliance with clicks,
you square,
there are several choices, guys, there are
smartftp, short stories, Merposnews, what
he saw was
only
there,
we check the program Maybe there are more
Transmart promos, testimonials too
Hi,
products in the individual insurance product
Lolo,
what
will be the results of the overhaul, the results are spoons, the
first Indonesian product specifically for
protection against the risk of cancer,
this is the age line for entry,
one month, one day up to 60 years old
Hi, there are
lots of Spas, this is
Lori, a Triyasa device
has a risk of cancer
this time, what is this,
individual family Okay, good spirit, rice,
individual health
and his family are also okay, okay, later we will
continue, let's end
here about insurance
in Indonesia, later we will hunt for
insurance again